Walking on Sunshine is a comedy, romance film directed by Dania Pasquini.
Set to the music of popular hit songs from the 1980s.
A beautiful coastal village, present day Italy.
After a whirlwind romance, Maddie is preparing to marry gorgeous Italian
Raf, and has invited her sister Taylor to the wedding.
Unbeknownst to Maddie, however, Raf is Taylor's
ex-holiday flame, and the love of her life...
Maddie, played by Annabel Scholey.
Taylor, played by Hannah Arterton.
Airport passenger, played by Kumud Pant.
Raf, played by Giulio Berruti.
Doug, played by Greg Wise.
Lil, played by Katy Brand.
Walking on Sunshine is a 2014 British romantic jukebox musical comedy-drama film directed by Max Giwa and Dania Pasquini,
and starring Annabel Scholey, Giulio Berruti, Hannah Arterton, Katy Brand and Leona Lewis in her film debut.
The film features covers of songs from the 1980s
and was released on 27 June 2014.
It is also a debut role for singer-songwriter Leona Lewis.
The film explores themes of spain, musical, europe, wedding, summer.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.